skybox.net 2019-05-17

# USPS

Privacy and Security Policy 

**Privacy Notice**  
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for **www.skybox.net**. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site.  
We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.  
We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.   
We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.   
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

**Your Access to and Control Over Information** You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: 

  * See what data we have about you, if any. 
  * Change/correct any data we have about you. 
  * Have us delete any data we have about you. 
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment

. **GDPR** Terms & Conditions

#### SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, Data Privacy Policy

SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, acknowledges the importance of Data Protection, and takes the responsibility to protect the customer’s data, and limit its usages within the agreement under which the data has been shared with SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”,. 

The data protection policy of SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, enforces that the data once shared with SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, is not used for any marketing purposes, and is not exposed to any external parties or business partners across the world unless prior consent of the customer is given

Below are the details of what data is received and saved by SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, for the purpose of fulfilling SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”,'s courier services of pickup and/or delivery of the shipments.

#### What Information does SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, Hold?

As a courier company, SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, receives the customer’s information for the purpose of pickup or delivery of the customer’s shipments. SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, collects the following information: Name, Address, Telephone number (Fixed Line), Mobile number, Email address, and signature at the time of delivery (optional).

#### Data Usage

SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, only collects, processes and utilizes personal data to the extent, which it is necessary to establish, maintain and terminate a contractual relationship, which was established in order to supply pick-up and/or delivery services to the customer. 

It is SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”,’s legitimate interest to process personal data in order to improve our service, to answer questions and to handle claims and complaints. 

#### Data Protection

SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”,’s Data Protection Policy ensures that we take adequate technical measures to protect the customer’s personal data from exposure to any external entity, theft, or misuse. The data shared with SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, is always saved in an internal operating environment which is not publically accessible. The data shared on the SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, website and shopping cart form [www.skybox.net](http://www.skynet.net/) is encrypted by Secure Socket Layer (SSL).

#### Data Retention and Destruction

SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, saves the personal information shared by the customer for a period of 10 years, after which the data is destroyed using proper data destruction tools. 

#### Subject Access Request (SAR)

SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, acknowledges the importance of the rights of a person to be forgotten, therefore we accept Subject Access Requests, in case you want to know what information SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, holds about you, and/or you want that information to be amended or destroyed from the SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, system.

To initiate a request to access, amend or erase your details in the SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, system please fill out the form below, and send an email to the following email address [compliance@skybox.net](mailto:compliance@skybox.net) along with a scanned copy of any of the following valid documents (driver’s license, birth certificate, passport, marriage certificate).

**Important Notices**

  * Subject Access Requests can only be initiated by the Subject (Person). Any Subject Access Requests received from a third party will not be entertained. SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, will verify the request details (Email, Telephone, and Address) prior to processing the request. 
  * The details will only be shared to the provided email address in a standard format, depending upon the type of request initiated by the Subject.
  * The processing time for the Subject Access Request may take a maximum of 40 days, although SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, will try to utilize its resources to complete the request earlier. 
  * The Details collected in the below form will only be used by SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, for the purpose of GDPR Subject Access Request, and will not be shared with any external parties. 

#### Subject Access Request Form (GDPR)

**Personal Details**

The details below must be duly filled by the Information owner, any request found to be initiated by a third party who does not own the requested information will not be processed. 

| Particular | Details | Remarks  
---|---|---  
Full Name | None | Should be the same as available on the legal ID provided in the email attachment.   
Email Address | To be filled by the customer |    
Telephone Number  | To be filled by the customer | (Fixed Line)  
Mobile Number | To be filled by the customer | Cuts vertical padding in half, from 8px to 4px, within all `td` and `th` elements  
Address | To be filled by the customer | (must be including the country code)  
Request Type | To be filled by the customer | Please write only one of these Access/Amend/Erase  
Reference Number | To be filled by the customer | Please provide any Reference number like Shipment Number  
  
**Request Details**

Please write some details about your request in the field below.  

**Important Notes:**

  * Please fill the details in the above form and email the same to [compliance@skybox.net](mailto:compliance@skybox.net) along with a scanned copy of any of the following valid documents (driving license, birth certificate, passport, marriage certificate).
  * SkyBOX (SkyBOX Inc) hereinafter referred to as “SkyBOX”, will review your request, and will take necessary actions as per the type of request within a maximum of 40 days after the request has been initiated.
